Guide to the General Accounting Services, Yale University, Monthly Accounting Statements
Yale University Library
Manuscripts and Archives
General Accounting Services, Yale University, monthly accounting statements
1976-1999
RU 1091
Yale University. Office of Finance and Administration..
52.75 linear feet (158 boxes)
The materials consist of microfiche copies of monthly accounting statements from General Accounting Services.
Forms part of Yale Record Group 5-B (YRG 5-B), Accounting records and records of the Yale comptroller.
Manuscripts and Archives Sterling Memorial Library 128 Wall Street P.O. Box 208240 New Haven, CT 06520 Web: http://www.library.yale.edu/mssa/ Email: mssa.assist@yale.edu Phone: (203) 432-1735 Fax: (203) 432-7441
Administrative Information
Provenance
The materials were transferred from General Accounting Services, 2008.
Information about Access
Access to the materials is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Information about the Creator(s)
General Accounting Operations Development is responsible for overseeing Labor Distribution, Grants Management, and Accounts Receivable, in addition to the General Ledger. The department is also responsible for establishing processes to ensure the proper integration of accounting. Additional responsibilities of GA Services include: establish the University's accounting calendar and oversee posting/closing activities; develop reconciliation processes/procedures that ensure effective integration of financial transactions; maintain COA values including PSOO and PTAEO; establish electronic transaction processing standards; and design quality assurance programs.
Description of the Papers
The materials consist of microfiche copies of monthly accounting statements from General Accounting Services.
Arrangement
The materials are arranged chronologically.
Collection Contents
- Monthly accounting statements, 1976-1999; Accession 2009-A-114
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2035.
  - 1976 Dec - 1977Jun (Box 1)
  - 1977 Jun - 1978 Jan (Box 2)
  - 1978 Feb - Jul (Box 3)
  - 1978 Aug - 1979 Mar (Box 4)
  - 1979 Mar - Jul (Box 5)
  - 1979 Aug - 1980 Jan (Box 6)
  - 1980 Feb - Jul (Box 7)
  - 1980 Jul - 1981 Jan (Box 8)
  - 1981 Feb - Oct (Box 9)
  - 1981 Nov - 1982 Jul (Box 10)
  - 1982 Jul - Dec (Box 11)
  - 1982 Dec - 1983 Jan (Box 12)
  - 1983 Feb (Box 13)
  - 1983 Mar - Apr (Box 14)
  - 1983 Apr - Aug (Box 15)
  - 1983 Sep - 1984 Feb (Box 16)
  - 1984 Mar - Jun (Box 17)
  - 1984 Jun - Dec (Box 18)
  - 1985 Jan - Feb (Box 19)
  - 1985 Mar - Apr (Box 20)
  - 1985 May - Jun (Box 21)
  - 1985 Jun (Box 22)
  - 1985 Jun - Jul (Box 23)
  - 1985 Aug - Sep (Box 24)
  - 1985 Oct - Nov (Box 25)
  - 1985 Nov - Dec (Box 26)
  - 1986 Jan - Jun (Box 27)
  - 1986 Jun - Sep (Box 28)
  - 1986 Oct (Box 29)
  - 1986 Nov - Dec (Box 30)
  - 1986 Dec - 1987 Apr (Box 31)
  - 1987 May - Jun (Box 32)
  - 1987 Jun - Oct (Box 33)
  - 1987 Oct - 1988 Feb (Box 34)
  - 1988 Feb - May (Box 35)
  - 1988 May - Jul (Box 36)
  - 1988 Aug - Sep (Box 37)
  - 1988 Oct - Nov (Box 38)
  - 1988 Nov - Dec (Box 39)
  - 1989 Jan - May (Box 40)
  - 1989 Jun - Aug (Box 41)
  - 1989 Aug - 1990 Jan (Box 42)
  - 1990 Feb - May (Box 43)
  - 1990 Jun - 1991 Mar (Box 44)
  - 1991 Apr - Dec (Box 45)
  - 1992 Jan - Apr (Box 46)
  - 1992 May - Jun (Box 47)
  - 1992 Jul (Box 48)
  - 1992 Aug (Box 49)
  - 1992 Sep (Box 50)
  - 1992 Oct (Box 51)
  - 1992 Nov (Box 52)
  - 1992 Dec (Box 53)
  - 1993 Jan (Box 54)
  - 1993 Feb (Box 55)
  - 1993 Mar (Box 56)
  - 1993 Apr (Box 57)
  - 1993 May (Box 58)
  - 1993 Jun (Box 59)
  - 1993 Jun - 1st balance (Box 60)
  - 1993 Jun - 2nd balance (Box 61)
  - 1993 Jun - 3rd balance (Box 62)
  - 1993 Jun - 4th balance (Box 63)
  - 1993 Jul (Box 74)
  - 1993 Aug (Box 64)
  - 1993 Sep (Box 65)
  - 1993 Oct (Box 66)
  - 1993 Nov (Box 67)
  - 1993 Dec (Box 68)
  - 1994 Jan (Box 69)
  - 1994 Feb (Box 70)
  - 1994 Mar (Box 71)
  - 1994 Apr (Box 72)
  - 1994 May (Box 73)
  - 1994 Jun (Box 75)
  - 1994 Jun - 1st balance (Box 76)
  - 1994 Jun - 2nd balance (Box 77)
  - 1994 Jun - 3rd - 4th balance (Box 78)
  - 1994 Jul (Box 79)
  - 1994 Aug (Box 80)
  - 1994 Sep (Box 81)
  - 1994 Oct (Box 82)
  - 1994 Nov (Box 83)
  - 1994 Dec (Box 84)
  - 1995 Jan (Box 85)
  - 1995 Feb (Box 86)
  - 1995 Mar (Box 87)
  - 1995 Apr (Box 88)
  - 1995 May (Box 89)
  - 1995 Jun (Box 90)
  - 1995 Jun - 1st balance (Box 91)
  - 1995 Jun - 2nd balance (Box 92)
  - 1995 Jun - 3rd - 4th balance (Box 93)
  - 1995 Jul (Box 94)
  - 1995 Aug (Box 95)
  - 1995 Sep (Box 96)
  - 1995 Oct (Box 97)
  - 1995 Nov (Box 98)
  - 1995 Dec (Box 99)
  - 1996 Jan (Box 100)
  - 1996 Feb (Box 101)
  - 1996 Mar (Box 102)
  - 1996 Apr (Box 103)
  - 1996 May (Box 104)
  - 1996 Jun (Box 105)
  - 1996 Jun - 1st balance (Box 106)
  - 1996 Jun - 2nd balance (Box 107)
  - 1996 Jun - 3rd - 4th balance (Box 108)
  - 1996 Jul (Box 109)
  - 1996 Aug (Box 110)
  - 1996 Sep (Box 111)
  - 1996 Oct (Box 112)
  - 1996 Nov (Box 113)
  - 1996 Dec (Box 114)
  - 1997 Jan (Box 115)
  - 1997 Feb (Box 116)
  - 1997 Mar (Box 117)
  - 1997 Apr (Box 118)
  - 1997 May (Box 119)
  - 1997 Jun (Box 120)
  - 1997 Jun - 1st balance (Box 121)
  - 1997 Jun - 2nd balance (Box 122)
  - 1997 Jun - 3rd balance (Box 123)
  - 1997 Jun - 4th balance (Box 124)
  - 1997 Jul (Box 125)
  - 1997 Aug (Box 126)
  - 1997 Sep (Box 127)
  - 1997 Oct (Box 128)
  - 1997 Nov (Box 129)
  - 1997 Dec (Box 130)
  - 1998 Jan (Box 131)
  - 1998 Feb (Box 132)
  - 1998 Mar (Box 133)
  - 1998 Apr (Box 134)
  - 1998 May (Box 135)
  - 1998 Jun (Box 136)
  - 1998 Jun - 1st balance (Box 137)
  - 1998 Jun - 2nd balance (Box 138)
  - 1998 Jun - 3rd balance (Box 139)
  - 1998 Jun - 4th balance (Box 140)
  - 1998 Jul (Box 141)
  - 1998 Aug (Box 142)
  - 1998 Sep (Box 143)
  - 1998 Oct (Box 144)
  - 1998 Nov (Box 145)
  - 1998 Dec (Box 146)
  - 1999 Jan (Box 147)
  - 1999 Feb (Box 148)
  - 1999 Mar (Box 149)
  - 1999 Apr (Box 150)
  - 1999 May (Box 151-152)
  - 1998 Jun (Box 153-154)
  - 1998 Jun - 1st balance (Box 155)
  - 1998 Jun - 2nd balance (Box 156)
  - 1998 Jun - 3rd balance (Box 157)
  - 1998 Jun - 4th balance (Box 158)